{
    "subject": "resource/Charles_de_Gaulle",
    "predicate": "ontology/battle",
    "object": "resource/Battle_of_Dinant",
    "human_readable": "Charles de Gaulle was involved in the Battle of Dinant.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.952258825302124,
            "question": "In which battle was Charles de Gaulle involved?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8403449058532715,
            "question": "What other battles was Charles de Gaulle involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.789121687412262,
            "question": "How did Charles de Gaulle's involvement impact the course of the battle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7605011463165283,
            "question": "Who was Charles de Gaulle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6543800830841064,
            "question": "Where was the Battle of Dinant fought?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6000075936317444,
            "question": "Who were the opposing forces in the Battle of Dinant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5197486877441406,
            "question": "What significant role did Charles de Gaulle play in history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44605422019958496,
            "question": "When did the Battle of Dinant take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.429744690656662,
            "question": "What were the key events of the Battle of Dinant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41259005665779114,
            "question": "What were the consequences of the Battle of Dinant?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Charles de Gaulle was involved in the Battle of Dinant.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4090_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the key events of the Battle of Dinant?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4090_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did the Battle of Dinant take place?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4090_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What significant role did Charles de Gaulle play in history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4090_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4090_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4090_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4090_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4090_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4090_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4090_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4090_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4090_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4090_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4090_68.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation result in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The text from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4090/re-ranker-msmarco/85.txt and other files confirm that Charles de Gaulle was indeed involved in the Battle of Dinant, where he received a bullet in the knee on August 15th, 1914."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support that Charles de Gaulle was involved in the Battle of Dinant, as evidenced by statements such as \"As a platoon commander, He received his baptism of fire on 15 August and was among the first to be wounded, receiving a bullet in the knee at the Battle of Dinant\" from the document `14.txt`."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}